Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Chairman's Subject Files, 1962-1988; 2; 6.5 cubic ft.
  - Elections, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Elections -- Canvasses of Votes (County/Towns), 1979; 3 folders (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Endorsement of Candidates, Requests, 1980; 1985 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Enrollment by Counties, 1963-1982 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Enrollment -- General, 1962-1965 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Enrollment in the Conservative Party, 1963-1972 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Enrollment -- U.S. Senate Vote, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Farber, Barry -- Validation of Designating Petition, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Friends of the Conservative Party, 1979-1982; 1986 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Friends Reception for Gov. Reagan, 1 Jan. 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Fund Appeal, 1963-1967; 1972-1976; 1980; 2 folders (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Fund Appeal -- Folder 3, 1964; 1966; 1974-1975; 1979; 1982 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Fund Raisers, 1971-1972; 1974; 1979; 1981 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Fund Raising, 1972-1975 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Fund Raising, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Fund Raising, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Fund Raising -- Annual Dinners, 1965-1966; 1968; 1970; 1975-1976 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Huntington Conservative Party Club, 1979 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1971 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1973 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1974 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1975 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Judicial District Convention, 1979 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Judicial District Conventions, 1982-1983; 1986 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Keating, Barbara -- Montages, 1974 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Lease -- Termination, 1979 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Legal Cases, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Legal Cases -- Abraham Hirschfield, 1976 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Legal Cases -- Federal Election Commission Order re: CPNYS State Committee/1984 Victory Fund, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Legal Cases -- Invalid Petitions, 1967-1968; 1970 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Legal Cases -- Islip Town Conservative Committee, 1979 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Legal Cases -- Order to Show Cause, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Legal Cases -- Ottinger vs. Lomenzo, Mahoney, et.al, 1970 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Legal Cases -- Frederick P. Roland, 1968 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Legal Cases -- Scalone v. Thaler, 1972 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Legal Cases -- Specification Against Validity of Candidate's Acceptance, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Alert, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Legislative Alert, 1977 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1971 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1973 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1974 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1975 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1977 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1979 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1980 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1985 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1986 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Legislative Program, 1963 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Legislative Program, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Legislative Program, 1965 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Program, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Legislative Program, 1967 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Program, 1968 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Program, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Legislative Program, 1970 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Legislative Program, 1971 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Legislative Program, 1972 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Legislative Program, 1973 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Legislative Program, 1974 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Legislative Program, 1975 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Legislative Program, 1976 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Legislative Program, 1977 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Legislative Program, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Legislative Program, 1986 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Legislative Program (CPNYS Silver Anniversary Year), 1987 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Legislative Program, 1988 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Legislative Reception and Political Action Conference, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1965-1967 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Mailings to State Executive Committee, County Chairman and Key Advisers, 1981 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Membership, Sustaining -- Conservative Party, 1980 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - National Affairs Conference, 1983 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - News Clipping Montages, 1965 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - News Clipping Montages, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - News Clipping Montages, 1975-1976 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Nomination of Candidates, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Nomination of Candidates, 1985 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Officers & Executive Committees (5 counties) -- Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Party Bylaws: Proposed Amendments, Undated (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - "Party Call", 1968 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - "Party Call": Kings County, 1968 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - "Party Call", 1969 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - "Party Call", 1970 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - "Party Call", 1971 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - "Party Call", 1972 April (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - "Party Call", 1973 March (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - "Party Call", 1974 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - "Party Call", 1975 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - "Party Call", 1976 January (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - "Party Call", 1976 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - "Party Call": Queens County, 1976 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - "Party Call", 1977 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - "Party Call", 1978 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - "Party Call", 1979 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - "Party Call", 1980 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - "Party Call": Cayuga County, 1980 May (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - "Party Call": Putnam County, 1980 June (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - "Party Call", 1986 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Party Enrollment, 1980 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Party Enrollment -- Queens, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Party Enrollment, 1985 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Party Poll Results, 1971 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Petition Instructions, 1964-1967 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Petition Instructions, 1968-1972 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Petition Instructions, 1973-1974; 1976-1980 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Petition Memorandum, 1986 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Petitions Committee -- Manhattan, 1985 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Petitions, Designating, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Bronx, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Kings & Queens Counties, 1965; 1968; 1970-1974 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Kings & Queens Counties, 1975-1980; 1985 (Box 5 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Nassau County, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Petitions, Designating -- New York City, 1977; 1981; 1984-1985 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Petitions, Designating -- New York County, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Primary, 1984 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Suffolk County, 1979 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Upstate Counties, 1977; 1982; 1984-1985 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Petitions, Designating -- Validate, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Petitions -- Issues, 1966; 1979-1980; 1984; 1986 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Petitions -- List Filed for Primary, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Petitions -- Removal of Judge Wright, 1979 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Petitions -- Smoler Petition, Alleged Forgeries on, Undated (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Police Memorial Day, 1971-1977 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Police Action Conference, CPNYS, 1979-1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Police Action Conference, CPNYS, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Police Action Conference, CPNYS, 1985 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Political Calendar, 1982 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Poster -- Anti-Welfare State, [1980] (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials (Various Issues), 1975 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials (Various Issues), 1977 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials (Various Issues), 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials (Various Issues), 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials -- Queens County CP (Various Issues), 1975-1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Report to Sustaining Members, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Requests for State Executive Committee Authorization, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Rules & Regulations -- County Committees, Undated (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Rules & Regulations -- CPNYS, 1964 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Rules & Regulations -- CPNYS, 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Rules & Regulations -- Proposed Changes, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Rules & Regulations, 1988 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28a)
  - State Committee (CPNYS), 1962 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - State Committee -- Calculations of % of Votes for Governor, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - State Committee -- County Chairmen Not State Committeemen, Undated (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - State Committee -- Election of Members, 12 September 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - State Committee -- Election of Officers, 24 April 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - State Committee -- Election of Officers, 23 September 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - State Committee -- Election of Officers, 20 September 1986 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - State Committee List, 1980-1982 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - State Committee Mailing, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - State Committee Officers List, 1983 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - State Committee -- 1980 Senate Race Endorsement (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - State Committee -- Rules & Regulations, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - State Committee -- Voting, 1966; 1974 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - State Committee Meeting, 7 September 1967 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - State Committee Meetings, 1968 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - State Committee Meeting, 4 September 1969 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - State Committee Meeting, 7 April 1970 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - State Committee Meeting, 4 June 1971 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - State Committee Meeting, 4 April 1972 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - State Committee Meeting, 1 July 1972 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - State Committee Meetings, 1972 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - State Committee Meeting, 12 March 1973 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - State Committee Meeting, 15 June 1974 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - State Committee Meeting, 21 September 1974; 2 folders (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 52-53)
  - State Committee Meeting, 21 April 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - State Committee Meeting, 12 June 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - State Committee Meeting, 18 September 1976 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - State Committee Meeting, 23 September 1978 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - State Committee Meeting, 14 June 1980 (Box 6 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - State Committees -- CPNYS & Republican, 1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - State Executive Committee -- Committee on Conservative Alternatives, 1975 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - State Executive Committee Meeting, 11 August 1977 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - State Executive Committee Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - State Executive Committee Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - State Executive Committee Meeting, 20 July 1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - State Executive Committee -- Membership, ca. 1981 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - State Executive Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1962-1988 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - State Executive Committee -- Montages, 1981 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - State Executive Committee -- Proposed Amendments to Rules and Election of Officers, 1980; 1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - State Executive Committee -- Statewide Officers, 1963-1964; 1966-1967 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State Convention, 14 June 1964 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - State Convention, 1965 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - State Convention, 1966 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - State Convention, 1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - State Convention, 1986 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Testimonial Dinner Committee -- Honoring J. Daniel Mahoney, ca. 1982 (Box 7 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
- Executive Director's Day Files, 1973; 3; 0.1 cubic ft.
  This series consists of outgoing correspondence and bulletins. The bulk of the material was created by the Executive Director of the Conservative Party of New York State, but includes some correspondence of the State Chairman.
  - Day File, 1973 January-1973 April (Box 1 (3-Executive Director's Day Files), Folder 1)
  - Day File, 1973 May-1973 December (Box 1 (3-Executive Director's Day Files), Folder 2)
- News Releases, 1962-1966; 1968-1981; 1983; 1986; 4; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains news releases issued by the Conservative Party of New York State for all years since the party's inception with the exception of 1982, 1984 and 1985. It contains information on Conservative Party candidates, New York State and New York City politicians, and social, political and economic issues.
  - News Releases, 1962 June-1962 October (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 1)
  - News Releases, 1962 October-1962 December (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 2)
  - News Releases, 1963 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 3)
  - News Releases, 1964 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 4)
  - News Releases, 1965 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 5)
  - News Releases, 1966 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 6)
  - News Releases, 1968 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 7)
  - News Releases, 1970 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 8)
  - News Releases, 1971 January-1971 July (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 9)
  - News Releases, 1971 July-1971 December (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 10)
  - News Releases, 1972 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 11)
  - News Releases, 1973 January-1973 October (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1973 October-1973 December (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 13)
  - News Releases, 1974 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 14)
  - News Releases, 1975 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1976 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 16)
  - News Releases, 1977 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 17)
  - News Releases, 1978 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 18)
  - News Releases, 1979 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 19)
  - News Releases, 1980 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 20)
  - News Releases, 1981 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 21)
  - News Releases, 1983 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 22)
  - News Releases, 1986 (Box 1 (4-News Releases), Folder 23)
- Publications, 1969-1987; 5; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains primarily dinner journals for the annual dinners of the Conservative Party of New York State, a newsletter issued by the CPNYS, Congressional Alert (1976/77, 1979), and the party's Political Action Manual (1969). The dinner journals contain lists of Conservative Party officials (state and county), sponsors, members and candidates.
  - Address by Paul L. Adams at the Annual Dinner of the New York County Committee, New York State Conservative Party, 22 February 1972 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Conservative Party Congressional Alert, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Conservative Party Congressional Alert, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Dinner Journal -- 13th Anniversary -- A Salute to Ronald Reagan, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Dinner Journal -- 15th Anniversary, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Dinner Journal -- 16th Anniversary, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Dinner Journal -- 18th Anniversary, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Dinner Journal, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Dinner Journal -- 20th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Dinner Journal -- 21st Anniversary, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Dinner Journal and Yearbook, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Dinner Journal -- 25th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Political Action Manual, 1969; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 13-14)
- Position Papers, 1964-1968; 1970-1973; 1977; 6; 0.25 cubic ft.
  This series contains statements or papers issued by the Conservative Party of New York State or CPNYS candidates on various issues such as taxes, busing, pollution control, prison reform, etc.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Campus Disorders -- by James L. Buckley, [1970] (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 1)
  - Capital Punishment, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 2)
  - Community Development Amendment (no. 1), 1971 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 3)
  - Conservation -- by James L. Buckley, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 4)
  - Crisis in the Schools -- Buckley (William) for Mayor HQ, [1965] (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 5)
  - Deliberate Tax Gap in Rockefeller Budget -- by Paul L. Adams, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 6)
  - Education, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 7)
  - Environmental Quality Bond Issue, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 8)
  - Fiscal Chaos -- Price of Mismanagement -- Buckley for Mayor HQ, 1965 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 9)
  - Narcotics, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Schools (Busing), [1964] (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 11)
  - New Business Tax -- Buckley for Mayor HQ, 1965 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 12)
  - Penal Codes -- by Mason Hampton, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 13)
  - Pollution Control, [1967] (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 14)
  - Prison Reform & Penal Reform, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 15)
  - Public Education, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 16)
  - School Prayer, Undated (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 17)
  - $750 Million Economic Action Program Bond Issue, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 18)
  - Sewer Indebtedness -- Amendment no. 2, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 19)
  - State Aid to Education, [1968] (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 20)
  - State Constitution, Undated (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 21)
  - State Finances, 1966 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 22)
  - State Finances, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 23)
  - State Taxes & Spending, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 24)
  - Transportation Bond Referendum, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 25)
  - Urban Development Corporation, Undated (Box 1 (6-Position Papers), Folder 26)
- Subject Files, 1962-1986; 7; 15 cubic ft.